Marco Talaat Basaly

PHP - WORDPRESS

2/8/2000

marcotalaat355@yahoo.com

L 01202937338

https://marco-talaat.netlify.app/

in marco-talaat-b349911a0

Profile Summary

WordPress Developer with +3 years of functional experience designing and managing business websites using WordPress creation tools. Skilled in frontend and back-end development and implementing themes and plugins. Successfully creates attractive and user-friendly websites to meet client expectations in agile environments. Built WordPress functions, creating custom post types and developing widgets to conform with Wordpress coding standards. Over +4 years of programming, javascript and ajax experience.

Experience

PHP - WORDPRESS iLamp Agency

9/2021 - Present

LaCosta Real Estate

Real estate multilanguage website, using custom ajax to make search criteria when you choose a developer in the developer menu, it will filter the projects menu according to the developer chosen I make it custom using ajax.

Powerful

For powerful international company contains a custom post type I made it using PHP code, not plugins this reduced number of plugins lead to enhanced performence of the website.

Katameros

Used custom post type like Powerful company.

• Expertise Globe

A form created from scratch using PHP and MySQL contains: admin page has full control and displays registered users with their details, you can accept or ignore registered users and it will send a custom email for users if accepted or ignored automatically, it also contains filter users upon anything. if you want to send a special certificate, for example, you can upload all certificates at one time and it will send for each one automatically based on ID or Phone number

PHP - WORDPRESS UpWork

2020 - 2021

- Created and updated re-usable code libraries to streamline WordPress development cycle
- Redesign layouts.

Front end developer

2019 - 2020

Freelancer.com

- Built a form connected with google sheets.
- Built responsive real estate website.
- Built and styled new mobile-friendly websites, transitioning legacy presentations to simultaneous easyto-use versions

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- BootStartp

- PHP
- A.JAX
- WordPress

Education

Veterinary medicine

Sohag University

Graduated